

## Contact

**Phone:** +48 889 549 270

Email: agatalipiak25@gmail.com

# Languages

English – B2

German - A1

# **Hobbies**

Culinary

**Brewing** 

Football

Martial Arts

Movies

Fitness

# **Agata Lipiak**

## **About me**

I am 27 years old and since last year I have been intensively learning programming in JavaScript in order to get a job as a Front-end Developer. I am a very mobilized person who achieves his goals, which is why I have successfully completed so many projects in my current job. Programming has become my passion and I would like to develop my skills in this direction.

#### **Skills**

- React, Redux, Styled Components
- JavaScript, ES6+
- GitHub
- CSS3
- HTML5
- Node.js + Express

- PostgreSQL
- Interpersonal skills
- Team work
- Work planning and organization
- Setting and achieving goals

# **Projects**

I used the knowledge and skills in programming to create the following projects:

**My portfolio** – a website presenting my programming skills. To create it, I used technologies such as React and Styled Components.

#### https://www.alipiak.com

**Recipe organizer** – a website designed for storing, adding and managing recipes. It also allows you to plan recipes for the day and prepare a shopping list. To create it, I used technologies such as React, Redux and Styled Components

#### https://www.alipiak.com/recipe

**Weather app** – a web application for checking the current weather in different cities, deploy on Heroku. I used React, Node.js + Express and PostgreSQL.

https://weather-app-db2020.herokuapp.com

## **Education**

Master of Engineering: Mechanical Engineering – 2016 – 2017

Wrocław University of Technology, Faculty of Mechanical Engineering, second-cycle, full-time

Bachelor of Engineering: Material Engineering - 2012 - 2016

Wrocław University of Technology, Faculty of Chemistry, first-cycle, full-time

# **Experience**

Product Engineer - march 2020 - current | STELWELD

Process Engineer – august 2017 – march 2020 | STELWELD